[MOANING AND PANTING]
Translation by,facebook.com/marwin.affan
[COUGHING]
[SIGHS]
Are you okay?
Kau baik-baik saja?
[GROANING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[GASPS]
[TRACTOR BEEPING]
WALT: You are a lifesaver.,JESSE: Yeah, man.
- Kau penyelamat.,- Yeah, man.
Yeah, we can't,thank you enough.
- Kau penyelamat.,- Yeah, man.,- Kami berterima kasih sekali.,- Tidak, hey, respek.
No, hey, mad--,Mad props.
- Kami berterima kasih sekali.,- Tidak, hey, respek.
I could have sworn,the guy said south.
Aku bersumpah orang tadi bilang selatan.
But then all of a sudden,we're off the main road
Aku bersumpah orang tadi bilang selatan.,Tapi tiba-tiba,kita sudah diluar jalur.
then I'm trying to read the map,while I'm driving,
Tapi tiba-tiba,kita sudah diluar jalur.,Aku melihat peta sambil,menyetir, arahan orang bodoh.
which is a bonehead manoeuvre.
Aku melihat peta sambil,menyetir, arahan orang bodoh.
And then all of a sudden, bam we're-- We're in that ditch.
Dan tiba-tiba, bam! kita sudah di parit.
Yeah, bam. I'm like "What the hell?",You know?
Yeah, bam. Aku bilang "Apa-apaan ini?".
Yes. Oh, yes and my coffee mug.,Of coffee? My mug of coffee.
Yeah, bam. Aku bilang "Apa-apaan ini?".,Ya. Oh, ya, dan cangkir kopiku.,Ya cangkir kopiku.
It spills all over my pants I mean-- Just a nightmare.
Tumpah ke celanaku,...,Mimpi buruk...
There's your Sony GPS I mean, for real.
Tumpah ke celanaku,...,Mimpi buruk...,Lalu GPS mu Maksudku, ya.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Lalu GPS mu Maksudku, ya.
Let's just...
Mari kita...
Like I said we couldn't be more grateful.
Seperti kubilang kami benar-benar bersyukur.
Can't we just,dump them here?
Tak bisakah mereka kita buang disini?
What and somebody finds them?
Apa, kemudian ditemukan orang?
Then what?
Apa, kemudian ditemukan orang?,Lalu apa?
People have seen us.
Ada yang melihat kita.
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Hey, you're--,You're gonna,flood it, man.
Hey, kau membanjirinya, kawan.
I'm not gonna flood it.,She's not going to flood all right?
Tak akan.,Ia akan baik-baik saja, oke?
We're just gonna stay positive right?
Selalu berpikiran positif, kan?
We're gonna clean up,this mess. And you, start.
Kita bisa membereskan ini.,Dan, mulai.
Goddamn it. See, you flooded it.
Ya Tuhan. Lihat, kau membanjirinya.
All right.
Baik.
All right. You know what?,The RV is going to start now.
Baik. Kau tau?,RV ini akan nyala sekarang.
The RV is going to start,right now.
Sekarang juga.
It's gonna start and,we're gonna drive it,over to your house.
Mesin akan hidup.,Dan kita menuju rumahmu.
My house?,Yes. Your house.
- Rumahku?,- Ya, rumahmu.,Kita mengendarainya kesana,dan parkir semalam.
We're gonna drive it over there,and park it overnight.,And then tomorrow--
Kita mengendarainya kesana,dan parkir semalam.,- Dan besok...,- Teman, jangan dirumahku.
Uh-uh, man, not my house.
- Dan besok...,- Teman, jangan dirumahku.
Shut up! Shut up!
Diam. Diam.
[COUGHING]
After we finish,cleaning up this mess,
Setelah selesaikan,ini semua...
we will go our separate ways.
...kita berpisah.
Our paths will never cross.
Jalan kita sendiri- sendiri.
And we will tell this to no one.
Dan kita takkan beritau kesiapapun.
Understood?
Paham?
Oh, what, I can talk now?
Oh, apa, Sekarang boleh bicara?
Fine. That goes double for me.
Baiklah. Untukku 2x lipat.
Okay. Okay.
Be good to me.
Baiklah padaku.
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
[ENGINE REVS]
BOTH:,Yes!
Yes!
[BOTH YELL]
Yes. Okay. Okay.
Thank you.
Terima kasih.
[RUSTLING AND CAN CLATTERS]
[MAN GROANS]
[MAN WHEEZING]
Oh, shit.
Oh, sial.
[♪♪♪]
[COUGHING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
SKYLER:,Walt?
Walt?
You coming out?
Kau keluar?
WALT:,Mm-hm.
Yeah, absolutely.
Ya, tentu.
WOMAN [ON TV]:,We got looky-loos,in both directions, Dan.
Terlalu banyak yang melihat,TKP, Dan.
Better plan on being late if,you're going in that direction.
Bersiaplah telat,untuk anda yang bekerja.
This is Lisa in the Skycopter,
Lisa melaporkan dari helikopter , Jalanan Albuquerque,akan macet beberapa jam kedepan.
we'll have more Albuquerque,traffic on the hour.
Hey, um, you wanna hear,something funny?
Hey, mau dengar lelucon?
We had a--,A faculty meeting,last Thursday
Kami mengadakan rapat fakultas,kamis kemarin...
and the topic was,senior-class photos
...dan topiknya,adalah: Foto Senior...
and how we had instituted,a new rule last year
...dan topiknya,adalah: Foto Senior...,...dan bagaimana kita merumuskan,peraturan baru ditahun lalu...
that seniors are allowed,to have photos taken
...bahwa senior,diperbolehkan untuk diambil fotonya...
by a photographer,of their choice.
...oleh fotografer pilihan mereka sendiri.
You know, not necessarily,the photographer
Bukannya,fotografer...
that the school hires, right?,So--
...yang kerja untuk sekolah...
[PHONE RINGING]
--Um, eh,
so anyway, uh some of the senior girls
Lalu, beberapa dari mereka...
were going to that, um Glamour Shots place
...menuju tempat bagus dimana,mereka akan difoto.
to have their photos taken.
And now they're bringing us,all these photos,
Dan sekarang mereka bawa,semua foto-foto ini...
and Joan Everman--,You know Joan.
...Joan Everman...,Kau kenal Joan.
--Suddenly has to go through,all these photos
- Tiba-tiba harus memeriksa,foto-foto itu...
and turn them down,because they show cleavage.
...kemudian menolaknya,karena banyak belahan dada.
Did you get enough,pancakes, sweetie?
Pancakenya cukup, sayang?
Yeah. I-- I'm good.
Ya. Cukup.
Okay.
WALT:,You know even the small-busted girls
Walaupun yang berpayudara kecil,bisa terlihat belahannya.
have cleavage.
Apparently there's some new type
Walaupun yang berpayudara kecil,bisa terlihat belahannya.,Sepertinya ada bra tipe baru...
of brassiere or something.
Sepertinya ada bra tipe baru...
[PHONE RINGING]
The Wonderbra.
It's the Wonderbra.,Yeah?
Itu the Wonderbra.,Yeah?
Okay.
[PHONE CONTINUES RINGING]
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
SKYLER [ON RECORDING]:,Hey, there.,You've reached Walt,
Hai. Anda menghubungi Walt Skyler and Walter Jr.
Skyler and Walter Jr.
We can't come to the phone,right now, so please,leave us a message.
Kami tak bisa mengangkat mohon tinggalkan pesan.
[MACHINE BEEPS]
JESSE [OVER MACHINE]:,Hello, Mr. White.
Hello, Mr. White.,Ini AT&T.
This is AT&T calling.
Are you happy with your current,long-distance service?
Anda puas dengan,layanan interlokal kami?
Because if you're not, I would,definitely really, really love
Karena bila tidak Saya ingin sekali untuk...
to talk to you,as soon as possible about--
...bicara dengan anda,secepatnya mengenai...
Hello? Hello? Hello this is Walter White,speaking.
...bicara dengan anda,secepatnya mengenai...,Halo, Ini saya Walter White.
You said he was,practically dead, okay?
Kau bilang ia,sudah mati, kan?
You said he would die,any minute.
Kau bilang ia mati dalam hitungan menit.
Listen, uh I am having breakfast
Begini, Saya sedang makan,bersama keluarga...
with my family right now
Begini, Saya sedang makan,bersama keluarga...,...dan saya tak menghargai,telpon anda ini.
and I-- I really don't,appreciate these sales calls.
...dan saya tak menghargai,telpon anda ini.
Well, too bad, man because guess what.
Well, sayang sekali, teman karena, coba tebak.
He's still not dead.
Ia belum mati. ,Aku menguping di RV.
I went and put my ear,to the RV.,I can hear him, like,
Aku menguping di RV.,Aku dengar dia seperti berguling-guling, oke?
rolling around in there all right?
Aku dengar dia seperti berguling-guling, oke?
I-- I-- I think he's awake, man.
Menurutku ia terbangun, teman.,Aku pikir ia mencoba kabur.
I think he's trying,to get loose.
Where the hell are you?,I'm freaking out over here.
Dimana kau?,Aku ketakutan disini.
WALT [WHISPERING]:,Calm down, damn it.
Dimana kau?,Aku ketakutan disini.,- Tenang, brengsek.,- Kau bantu aku bereskan ini?
Are you gonna help me,clean this up?
- Tenang, brengsek.,- Kau bantu aku bereskan ini?
Huh? We got loose ends here.
- Kita punya kepentingan disini.,- Tenang.
Calm down.
I will be there after school.
Aku kesana sepulang kerja.
Huh, after school.,Are you shitting me?
Setelah kerja. Kau bercanda?
Ditch it, man. Call in sick.
Boloslah. Pura-pura sakit.
[IN USUAL TONE],Listen, uh, that is just,not gonna work for me.
Dengar, tak bisa,begitu.
I'm-- I'm not interested,in that at all.
Saya tak tertarik dengan itu.
And, uh, I would appreciate it,if you don't call here anymore.
Dan saya hargai bila anda,tak menelepon kesini lagi.
Damn.,They're so annoying those people.
Sial. Mereka sangat mengganggu.
You have a good day, sweetie.
- Semoga harimu baik, sayang.,- Okay, Bu. Kau juga.
Okay, Mom. You too.
Okay.,Bye, honey.
- Semoga harimu baik, sayang.,- Okay, Bu. Kau juga.,Bye, honey.
Drive safe.,Okay.
- Hati-hati.,- Okay.
[DIALLING]
[PHONE RINGS]
JESSE [OVER MACHINE]:,Yo, yo, yo,
Yo, yo, yo, 1, 4, 8, 3 to the 3,to the 6 to the 9, mewakili ABQ.
1, 4, 8, 3 to the 3,to the 6 to the 9,
representing the ABQ.
Yo, yo, yo, 1, 4, 8, 3 to the 3,to the 6 to the 9, mewakili ABQ.
What up, beyotch?,Leave it at the tone.
Ada apa, biatch?,Setelah nada.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
So the term "chiral"
Istilah "chiral"...
derives from the Greek word,"hand."
...berasal dari bahasa,Yunani "tangan".
Now, the concept here,being that
Konsepnya adalah bahwa,tangan kiri dan kananmu...
just as your left hand,and your right hand
are mirror images,of one another, right,
...seperti pantulan kaca serupa, dan juga berlawanan arah...
identical and yet opposite,
well, so, too organic compounds can exist
...well, begitu juga senyawa organik bisa hidup...
as mirror-image forms,of one another
...sebagai pantulan bentuk,satu dan yang lainnya...
all the way down,at the molecular level.
...sampai ke level molekul terbawah.
But although they may,look the same,
Tapi, walaupun kelihatannya sama..
they don't always,behave the same.
...mereka tak berperilaku sama.
For instance...
Sebagai contoh...
Contoh.
Uh, I'm sorry.,Uh, for instance, uh...
Maaf. Contohnya...
Thalidomide.
The-- The right-handed isomer,of the drug thalidomide
Isomer kanan,dari obat thalidomide...
is a perfectly fine good medicine
...bagus sekali, obat yang baik...
to give to a pregnant woman,to prevent morning sickness.
...diberikan untuk ibu hamil,sebagai pencegah mual pagi.
But make the mistake of giving,that same pregnant woman
Tapi, suatu kesalahan,memberi ibu tersebut...
the left-handed isomer,of the drug thalidomide
...Isomer kiri,dari obat thalidomide...
and her child will be born,with horrible birth defects.
...dan anaknya akan terlahir,cacat/pincang.
Which is precisely,what happened in the 1950s.
Seperti yang terjadi,di tahun 50an.
So chiral, chirality,
So chiral, chirality bayangan cermin, kan?
mirrored images, right?
Active, inactive, good, bad.
Aktif, in-aktif, baik, buruk.
Uh, so.
So.
Yes, Ben.
- Ya, Ben.,- Ini akan ada di pembunuhan?
Is this gonna be,on the murder?
What?
Apa?
Is this gonna be,on the midterm?
Ini akan ada di ujian?
Uh, chirality on the midterm?
Chirality di ujian?,Tidak,... Well, mungkin.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
No, no. Well, maybe.,Maybe. Yes, you know--
Chirality di ujian?,Tidak,... Well, mungkin.,Mungkin. Ya, kau tau...,Persiapkan saja kemungkinan ada di ujian.
But prepare for it,to be on the midterm.
Mungkin. Ya, kau tau...,Persiapkan saja kemungkinan ada di ujian.
Can't hurt to know it, right?,So--
Agar aman, kan? So...
Knowledge is power.
Pengetahuan adalah kekuatan.
[♪♪♪]
[DOOR CREAKS THEN SLAMS]
[GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
Oh, no. Oh, no, no. No.
Oh, tidak. Oh, tidak, tidak.
Not good.,Not good, not good.
Tak bagus. Tak bagus.
[CLYDE McPHATTER'S,"YOU'RE MOVIN' ME",PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[TYRES SCREECH]
What the--?
Apa yang...?
[GASPING]
[WHEEZING]
Hey. Hey. Hey, you.
Hey. Hey. Hey, kau.
Hey, listen, you.
Hey. Hey. Hey, kau.,Hey, kau, dengar.
No, no, no, no!
Hey, kau, dengar.,Tidak, tidak!
Oh, God.
Oh, Tuhan.
Okay.
[TRUMP'S "KEEP BALLIN"',PLAYING ON COMPUTER]
MILFs?
MILF?
The hell is a MILF?
Apa itu MILF?
[KRAZY-8 WHEEZING]
[SNORING]
Now what?
Bagaimana sekarang?
[KRAZY-8 COUGHING]
Lock the other one,out in the RV.
Lihat yang satunya di RV.
He's, uh:
Lihat yang satunya di RV.,Dia...
You're sure?,Yes.
Dia...,- Kau yakin?,- Ya.
You're positive?,Hey, you know what?
- Positif yakin?,- Kau tau?
Feel free to go,check it yourself.
- Positif yakin?,- Kau tau?,- Periksalah sendiri.,- Ide bagus. Mungkin harus kulakukan...
Hey, yeah, Good idea.,Maybe I should do that
- Periksalah sendiri.,- Ide bagus. Mungkin harus kulakukan...
before he, too, wanders off,down the damn street.
...sebelum ia, juga, keluyuran,dijalanan.
Okay, you know what?,I am sick--
...sebelum ia, juga, keluyuran,dijalanan.,- Okay, Kau tau? Aku muak...,- Baiklah.
Just-- All right.,All right!
- Okay, Kau tau? Aku muak...,- Baiklah.
Just--
- Okay, Kau tau? Aku muak...,- Baiklah.,Baik...
The one downstairs tell me about him.
Baik...,Yang di basement ceritakan tentangnya.
Oh, come on. Anything.,Something.
Oh, ayolah. Semua. Sesuatu.,Mulai dari nama.
Start with his name at least.
Krazy-8.
Oh, ayolah. Semua. Sesuatu.,Mulai dari nama.,Krazy-8.
Krazy-8. What the hell,does that even mean?
Krazy-8.,Krazy-8.,Apa maksudnya?
I don't know, man, okay?
Krazy-8.,Apa maksudnya?,Aku tak tau, teman, okay? Artinya seperti, Crazy-8, okay? Aku tak tau.
It means, like-- Like Krazy-8, okay? I don't know.
Aku tak tau, teman, okay? Artinya seperti, Crazy-8, okay? Aku tak tau.
So you work with him regularly.
Aku tak tau, teman, okay? Artinya seperti, Crazy-8, okay? Aku tak tau.,Jadi biasanya kau kerja untuknya.
No, not him so much.
Jadi biasanya kau kerja untuknya.,Bukan dia sebenarnya.
His cousin, mainly.,Who's his cousin?
Bukan dia sebenarnya.,- Sepupunya.,- Siapa sepupunya?
The-- The guy out in the RV.
- Sepupunya.,- Siapa sepupunya?,- Yang di RV.,- Baik, baik, oke.
All right, all right all right.
- Yang di RV.,- Baik, baik, oke.
Krazy-8's one level higher.
- Yang di RV.,- Baik, baik, oke.,Krazy-8 satu level diatasnya.
One level higher.
Krazy-8 satu level diatasnya.,1 level lebih tinggi.
Yeah, you know.,Not, like, street level. Higher.
1 level lebih tinggi.,Yeah, kau tau.,Bukan seperti level jalanan, lebih tinggi.
You know how there's, like a Starbucks on every corner?
Yeah, kau tau.,Bukan seperti level jalanan, lebih tinggi.,Kau tau ada Starbucks di setiap sudut kota?
Krazy-8 is like the dude,that sells Starbucks' beans.
Kau tau ada Starbucks di setiap sudut kota?,Krazy-8 seperti yang menjual,biji kopinya.
Okay, so he's a distributor.
Krazy-8 seperti yang menjual,biji kopinya.,Okay, jadi ia distributor.
Okay, so is he...?,I mean, is...?
Okay, jadi dia? Maksudku...
In other words, what is his,reputation for violence?
Okay, jadi dia? Maksudku...,Dengan kata lain apa reputasinya dalam kekerasan?
Well, um, he did try
Well, dia mencoba bunuh kita,kemarin, seperti itu.
to kill us both yesterday so there's that.
Look, what I'm trying to say
Well, dia mencoba bunuh kita,kemarin, seperti itu.,Dengar, yang coba aku katakan,ia distributor, kan?
is that he's a distributor right?
Dengar, yang coba aku katakan,ia distributor, kan?
He's a-- He's a businessman.,He's a man of business.
Dengar, yang coba aku katakan,ia distributor, kan?,Ia bisnisman.,Orang yang berbisnis.
It would therefore,seem to follow that he is
Ia bisnisman.,Orang yang berbisnis.,Dan sepertinya ia...
capable of acting out of,mutual self-interest, yes?
Dan sepertinya ia...,...sanggup menimbal balik,kepentingan pribadi, kan?
What?
...sanggup menimbal balik,kepentingan pribadi, kan?,Apa?
Do you think he is capable,of listening to reason?
Apa?,Menurutmu ia bisa,mendengarkan sebuah alasan?
I mean, what--? What kind,of reason? You mean, like,
Alasan bagaimana? Seperti "Dear Krazy-8, hey, dengar...
"Dear Krazy-8, hey, listen if I let you go,
Alasan bagaimana? Seperti "Dear Krazy-8, hey, dengar...,...jika kau kulepaskan, kau janji,takkan kembali atau menghabisi seluruh keluargaku?
you promise not to come back,and waste my entire family?
...jika kau kulepaskan, kau janji,takkan kembali atau menghabisi seluruh keluargaku?
No Colombian neckties?",You mean that kind of reason?
...jika kau kulepaskan, kau janji,takkan kembali atau menghabisi seluruh keluargaku?,Tanpa dasi Colombia?",Berunding seperti itu?
No, man, I can't say as I have,high fucking hopes
Tanpa dasi Colombia?",Berunding seperti itu?,Tidak, teman, Aku tak bisa bilang punya,harapan tinggi tentang itu.
where that's concerned.
Tidak, teman, Aku tak bisa bilang punya,harapan tinggi tentang itu.
[THUMP]
[WHISPERING],What was that?
Apa itu?
What was what?,Shh!
Apa?
[CREAKING]
Come!,What?
We didn't tie him up.
Kita tak mengikatnya.
Why the hell,didn't we tie him up?
Kita tak mengikatnya.,- Kenapa kita tak mengikatnya?,- Oh, Tuhan.
Oh, God.
- Kenapa kita tak mengikatnya?,- Oh, Tuhan.
Because he was out cold.
- Kenapa kita tak mengikatnya?,- Oh, Tuhan.,- Karena dia sudah pingsan.,- Yeah, tapi kalau pura-pura?
Yeah, but what--,What if he's faking it?
- Karena dia sudah pingsan.,- Yeah, tapi kalau pura-pura?
You know, like if it was me,
- Karena dia sudah pingsan.,- Yeah, tapi kalau pura-pura?,Seperti, kalau aku jadi dia Aku akan pura-pura pingsan, Yo.
I'd be all faking,being knocked out, yo.
Seperti, kalau aku jadi dia Aku akan pura-pura pingsan, Yo.
And then when the coast is clear,
Lalu, ketika keadaan aman Aku akan mencari senjata.
I'd be up looking,for weapons and shit.
Ready to pounce.
Lalu, ketika keadaan aman Aku akan mencari senjata.,Bersiap menghajar.
[KRAZY-8 GROANING]
Bersiap menghajar.
[♪♪♪]
Shh, shh, shh.
[WHEEZING]
No, see. Now, if it was me
Lihat. Kalau aku jadi dia...
and I couldn't find,a decent enough weapon,
Lihat. Kalau aku jadi dia...,...dan tak menemukan,senjata yang bagus...
I would just lie back down,and bide my time.
...dan tak menemukan,senjata yang bagus...,...Aku lanjutkan berbaring,dan menunggu.
[GRUNTING]
So now what do we do?
Jadi, apa yang harus kita lakukan?
You keep asking me that
Kau tanya itu terus,seperti aku punya jawabannya.
like you think I have,some answer.
Well, you gotta,do something.
- Well, kau harus lakukan sesuatu.,- Kita.
No, we.
We have got to do something and I am open to suggestions.
Kita harus lakukan sesuatu dan silahkan memberi saran.
Man, uh, okay this whole thing was your deal.
Kita harus lakukan sesuatu dan silahkan memberi saran.,Man, okay ini semua idemu.
Don't you dare put that on me.
Man, okay ini semua idemu.,Beraninya kau menyalahkan aku.
You brought those guys,out there.
Kau yang membawa mereka.,Ini tanggung jawabmu.
This is your responsibility.
Oh, like I came to you begging to cook meth.
Kau yang membawa mereka.,Ini tanggung jawabmu.,Seperti aku mendatangimu memohon memasak meth.
"Oh, hey, nerdiest old dude,I know,
Seperti aku mendatangimu memohon memasak meth.,"Oh, hey, orang tua teraneh kau ingin masak meth?" Tolong.
you wanna come cook crystal?",Please.
"Oh, hey, orang tua teraneh kau ingin masak meth?" Tolong.
I'd ask my diaper-wearing granny
"Oh, hey, orang tua teraneh kau ingin masak meth?" Tolong.,Aku memohon ke nenekku,yang memakai popok...
but her wheelchair,wouldn't fit in the RV.
Aku memohon ke nenekku,yang memakai popok...,...tapi kursi rodanya tak cukup,masuk RV.
What about the, uh--,The-- The-- The phosphate gas?
Bagaimana dengan Gas phosphate?
The phosphine gas.,What about it?
Bagaimana dengan Gas phosphate?,Gas Phosphine. Kenapa?
Well, do-- I mean, do you think,it still might kill him?
Gas Phosphine. Kenapa?,Maksudku, menurutmu,masih bisa membunuhnya?
You know, with, like a delayed reaction or something?
Maksudku, menurutmu,masih bisa membunuhnya?,Kau tau kan, dengan, seperti reaksi yang tertunda atau?
I-- I don't know.
Aku tak tau.
You're supposed,to be a scientist.
Aku tak tau.,- Kau kan ilmuwannya.,- Begini.
Look, this isn't even,the issue
- Kau kan ilmuwannya.,- Begini.,Harusnya ini bukan masalah,yang membutuhkan perhatian utama.
that demands,immediate attention.
Harusnya ini bukan masalah,yang membutuhkan perhatian utama.
We have got a body in that RV.
Harusnya ini bukan masalah,yang membutuhkan perhatian utama.,Kita punya mayat di RV.,Dan diluar semakin hangat.
And it's getting warmer outside.
Kita punya mayat di RV.,Dan diluar semakin hangat.
Understand?
Mengerti?
And we have got to,do something about that soon.
Mengerti?,Dan kita harus,lakukan sesuatu secepatnya.
And in a way that,no one will ever find it.
Dan kita harus,lakukan sesuatu secepatnya.,Dan dengan cara,yang tidak seorangpun akan menemukannya.
Now, that-- That last part,is very, very important.
Dan dengan cara,yang tidak seorangpun akan menemukannya.,Bagian terakhir itu,yang sangat, sangat penting.
Therefore, it seems to me
Bagian terakhir itu,yang sangat, sangat penting.,Untuk itu, menurutku...
that our best course of action
...tindakan terbaik kita,adalah pelaburan secara kimia.
would be chemical,disincorporation.
Dissolving in strong acid.
Melarutkan dengan cairan kimia.
Oh, man, that's messed up.
Oh, teman, itu kacau.
I mean, ahem you're not serious.
Kau tak serius kan?
You serious?
Kau serius?
[SIGHS]
Well, who's gonna do that?
Well, siapa yang akan melakukan?
And don't look at me.
Well, siapa yang akan melakukan?,Dan jangan lihat aku.
I guess we'll both do it,together.
Kita lakukan bersama.
No, Mr. White, okay, I'm not--,I'm not good with dead bodies.
Kita lakukan bersama.,Tidak, Mr. White, okay Aku tidak bagus dalam urusan mayat.
Look, we are in this,fifty-fifty. Okay?
Tidak, Mr. White, okay Aku tidak bagus dalam urusan mayat.,Dengar, kita berdua bersama-sama. Okay?
I guess the only other fair way,to go about this would be
Kurasa cara lain terbaik,untuk ini adalah...
that one of us deals with,the body situation
Kurasa cara lain terbaik,untuk ini adalah...,...salah satu menangani,mayat...
while the other one of us deals,with the Krazy-8 situation.
...salah satu menangani,mayat...,...sedang satunya menangani,masalah Krazy-8...
In a scenario like this I don't suppose it is bad form
Di skenario seperti ini Aku tak menganggap melempar koin...
to just flip a coin.
Di skenario seperti ini Aku tak menganggap melempar koin...,...sebuah keputusan yang buruk.
Heads or tails?
- Kepala atau ekor?,- Tidak, Aku kerjakan yang mayat, okay?
No, I'll-- I'll do the body,in the acid, okay?
Heads or tails?
- Kepala atau ekor?,- Tidak, Aku kerjakan yang mayat, okay?,Kepala atau ekor?
Heads. Heads.
Kepala, kepala.
Best two out of three?
Tiga kali?
[PHONE RINGING]
JESSE [ON RECORDING]:,Yo, yo, yo, 1, 4, 8, 3 to the 3
Yo, yo, yo, 1, 4, 8, 3 to the 3,to the 6 to the 9, mewakili ABQ.
to the 6 to the 9 representing the ABQ.
What up, beyotch?,Leave it at the tone.
Ada apa, biatch?,Setelah nada.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
JESSE:,Hey, Mr. White, it's me.,Pick up.
Hey, Mr. White, ini aku. Angkatlah.
I got a container question.
Hey, Mr. White, ini aku. Angkatlah. ,Aku punya pertanyaan.
Hello, Mr. White.,Pick up the phone, man.
Halo, Mr. White.,Angkat teleponnya, teman.
Yes.,Yo, what kind of plastic, man?
Halo, Mr. White.,Angkat teleponnya, teman. ,- Ya.,- Yo, plastik yang bagaimana, man?
[OVER PHONE],Polyethylene.
- Ya.,- Yo, plastik yang bagaimana, man?,Polyethylene.
Well, how the hell am I,supposed to know that?
Bagaimana aku bisa tau itu?
Because I told you.
Bagaimana aku bisa tau itu?,Karena aku memberitaumu.
Look, just...
Karena aku memberitaumu.,Lihat, dibagian bawahnya,ada segitiga...
[SIGHS]
Lihat, dibagian bawahnya,ada segitiga...
look at the bottom,for a triangle
stamped LDPE.
Lihat, dibagian bawahnya,ada segitiga...,...tertera LDPE.
It should be moulded,right into the plastic.
...tertera LDPE.,Harusnya ada di plastiknya.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, LDPE.,Right on, got it.
Harusnya ada di plastiknya. ,Yeah, yeah, yeah, LDPE.,Dapat.
I don't know, man.,This feels kind of flimsy.
Tak tau, teman.,Sepertinya terlalu tipis.
Any decent acid's,gonna eat right through this.
Cairan kimia biasapun,sepertinya akan menembusnya.
Not hydrofluoric.,Why not?
Cairan kimia biasapun,sepertinya akan menembusnya.,- Tidak untuk hydrofluoric.,- Mengapa tidak?
Look, you skipped clowned around
Dengar, kau melewatkan tak serius...
or otherwise jerked off through,every lecture I ever gave.
Dengar, kau melewatkan tak serius...,...atau juga tak menghiraukan,setiap yang aku bilang.
As far as I'm concerned your chemistry education is over.
...atau juga tak menghiraukan,setiap yang aku bilang.,Sejauh yang kukawatirkan pelajaran kimiamu tamat.
Oh, okay, be a dick about it.,Jesus.
Sejauh yang kukawatirkan pelajaran kimiamu tamat.,Oh, okay, menjengkelkan. Tuhan.
So, hey, have you, um...?
So, hey, kau sudah lakukan itu?
Have you done the--?,The thing?
Yeah, I'm--
Ya, sedang akan kulakukan.
I'm working up to it.
[WHISPERING],You know what?
Kau tau?,Kurasa ia takkan bangun.
I bet he doesn't even wake up.
You know, not even,if you took him,to the hospital right now.
Bahkan walaupun sekarang,kau bawa ke RS.
Now, if it was me,
Kalau aku jadi kau aku akan berpikiran...
I would just try and think of it,like I was--
Kalau aku jadi kau aku akan berpikiran...,...seperti sedang membantunya.
I was doing him a favour.
...seperti sedang membantunya.
[BEEPS]
MAN [OVER PA]:,I need a check approval,on checkstand eight.
Approval on checkstand eight please. Thank you.
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
KRAZY-8:,Who's there?
Siapa itu?
What, you fucking break in?,Show me who's there.
Apa, kau menerobos masuk?,Tunjukkan siapa disana.
Yeah. I see you.
Ya. Kulihat kau.
What you gonna do?
Apa yang akan kau lakukan?
Hey.
Hey--!
Hey...!
[COUGHING]
Hey!
Hey.
I need water.
Aku butuh air.
[COUGHING]
Hey, hello.
Hey, halo.
Bring me some water would you?
Bawakan air, tolong?
[COUGHING]
Please.
You don't like the crust?
Tak suka pinggirannya?
Where's my cousin Emilio?
Mana sepupuku Emilio?
He dead?
Ia mati?
[DOOR SLAMS]
[KRAZY-8 COUGHING]
Oh, I'm a coward.
Oh, Pengecut.
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
[COUGHING]
[DOOR OPENS]
JESSE:,Hey, Mr. White.
Hey, Mr. White. Hey, Mr. White?
Hey, Mr. White?
Oh, fuck.
[CHUCKLING]
Are you smoking weed?,Oh, my God.
Kau mengganja? Ya Tuhan.
Wait a minute, is that--?,Is that my weed?
Tunggu, itu ganjaku?
What the hell, man?
Apa-apaan, man? Kenapa tak pakai,punyamu sendiri?
Make yourself at home why don't you?
So, what'd you end up buying?
- So, apa saja yang kau beli?,- Tak ada.
Nothing.
No store in town sells a plastic,bin big enough for a body.
Tak ada toko yang jual plastik,yang sebesar badan.
I don't suppose,you could buy two bins?
Bukankah bisa,beli 2?
And, uh, just:
Dan:
Legs in one torso in the other?
Kaki disana, tubuh disatunya?
Oh, God.
Oh, Tuhan.
I don't suppose,you could kiss my ass?
Harusnya,kau cium pantatku?
[SIGHS]
So, uh,
So...
how'd it--? How'd it go?
...bagaimana?
[KRAZY-8 COUGHING]
You didn't do it?
- Kau tidak melakukannya?,- Belum.
Not-- Not yet.
Oh, God.
Ya Tuhan.
Oh, damn. I gotta go.,Hey, hey.
- Oh, sial. Aku harus pergi.,- Hey, hey.
What? No, no, no.,Come back here.
- Oh, sial. Aku harus pergi.,- Hey, hey.,Apa? Tidak, tidak. Balik sini.
Sorry. I'll do it tomorrow I promise.
- Sorry. Akan kulakukan besok, Janji.,- Besok.
Tomorrow?
I've got a doctor's appointment.,I gotta go.
Aku ada janji dokter.,Harus segera pergi.
Look, stay away from him.,He's awake.
Dengar, menjauh darinya.,Ia sadar.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, man, we flipped a coin.
Hey, teman, kita sudah melempar koin.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[KRAZY-8 COUGHING]
Kita melempar koin.
We flipped a coin!
We're-- We're good?
Baik-baik saja?
We're very good.,We're excellent, I'd say.
Kita baik.,Sangat baik, menurutku.
Oh.
Oh, would you look,at that face?
Oh, lihatlah wajahnya?,Senyumlah, kecil.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
Smile, peanut.
Oh, lihatlah wajahnya?,Senyumlah, kecil.
So who's up for knowing?
Jadi, ingin mengetahui?
Oh...,Uh...
[BOTH LAUGH]
It's-- It's...,Uh...
Itu...
Yeah.
Girl.
- Perempuan.,- Perempuan?
Girl?
You sure?,OB-GYN: Pretty sure.
- Perempuan.,- Perempuan?,- Kau yakin?,- Cukup yakin.
[BOTH LAUGH]
- Kau yakin?,- Cukup yakin.
Wow.
Oh, God. Can I tell you that's exactly what I was hoping.
Tuhan. Kau tau tepat seperti yang kuinginkan.
Yeah?,Yeah.
- Ya?,- Yeah.
You remember you said that,when she's 16 and starts dating.
Ingatlah itu ketika ia,umur 16 dan mulai kencan.
[SKYLER LAUGHS]
OB-GYN:,Looking fabulous.
Menakjubkan. Jika mereka,selesai mengecek gula darah...
Let me see if they're done,with the blood sugar,
then we'll get you out of here.,I'll be right back.
...lalu anda boleh pulang.,Aku akan kembali.
Who's Jesse Pinkman?
Siapa Jesse Pinkman?
Jesse...?
- Jesse?,- Jesse Pinkman.
Jesse Pinkman.
He-- He called,just this morning.
Ia menelepon pagi tadi.
Walt, please don't deny it.
- Walt, tolong jangan menyangkal.,- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It-- It says on his MyShout page,he attended Wynne.
- Walt, tolong jangan menyangkal.,- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.,Di halaman MyShout,dia lulusan Wynne.
What, was he one,of your students?
- Salah satu muridmu?,- Yeah.
Yeah.
He was nobody.
Dia bukan siapa-siapa.
Who--? Who is he to you?,Why--? Why is he calling?
Ia apamu? Mengapa menelepon?,Apa ini rahasia besar...
What is this big secret
you seem to be discussing,with some druggie burnout?
...kau seperti diskusi,dengan pemakai ganja?
You don't come home last night,until 2 in the morning.
Kau tak pulang semalam sampai pukul 2,pagi. Jangan bilang...
You don't tell me,where you've been.
...kau darimana. Kau semalaman,di kamar mandi, Walt.
You spent the entire night,in the bathroom, Walt.
Tell me what's going on,with you.
Beritauku ada apa denganmu.,Kau kira tak hutang itu padaku?
Don't you think,you owe me that?
Who is this Jesse Pinkman,to you?
Siapa Jesse Pinkman ini?
He sells me pot.
Ia menjual ganja padaku.
He sells you pot?
- Ganja untukmu?,- Marijuana, yeah.
Marijuana, yeah.
Not a lot.,I mean, I don't know.
Tak banyak. Tak tau...
[SIGHS]
I kind of like it.
Sepertinya aku suka.
Are you out of your mind?
Apa kau sudah gila?,Kau umur 16an?
What--? What are you, like 16 years old?
Your brother-in-law,is a DEA agent.
Adik iparmu agen DEA.,Ada apa denganmu?
What--?,What is wrong with you?
Look, Skyler,
Begini, Skyler...
[SIGHS]
I just haven't,quite been myself lately.
...Akhir-akhir ini aku,tak seperti biasanya.
Yeah. No shit.,Thanks for noticing.
- Ya tak heran. Trims sudah mengingatkan.,- Aku bukan diriku sebenarnya...
I haven't been myself lately,
but I love you.
...tapi aku sayang kau.
Nothing about that,has changed.
...tapi aku sayang kau.,Perasaanku ke kau takkan berubah.,Takkan.
Nothing ever will.
Perasaanku ke kau takkan berubah.,Takkan.
So right now, what I need
Perasaanku ke kau takkan berubah.,Takkan.,Jadi sekarang, yang kubutuhkan...
is for you to climb down,out of my ass.
...kau jangan campuri,urusanku.
Can you do that?
Bisa kaulakukan?,Kau bisa kan, honey?
Will you do that for me, honey?
Will you please, just once,
Tolong, sekali ini saja jangan campuri urusanku?
get off my ass?
You know.
Tolong, sekali ini saja jangan campuri urusanku?,Kau tau.
I'd appreciate it.,I really would.
Kau tau.,Aku akan sangat menghargainya.
Stop.
Berhenti.
Stop in-- In 15 minutes.
Stop 15 menit lagi.
[COUGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[SNORTS]
SHEMP [OVER TV]:,Your face is too sharp.
Wajahmu terlalu tampan.
MOE [OVER TV]:,Powder. Powder!
Bedak. Ambil,bedak! Cepat.
SHEMP:,Take a powder, go on.
[KRAZY-8 COUGHING]
Bedak. Ambil,bedak! Cepat.
MOE:,Nice. Beautiful talcum powder.
Bagus. Bedak yang bagus.,Kau beruntung, no 8.
Lucky you, number eight.
[SNEEZES]
Bagus. Bedak yang bagus.,Kau beruntung, no 8.
Just meat, it's all just--,Just a bunch of meat.
Hanyalah daging hanya seonggok daging.
[FLIES BUZZING]
Oh, Jesus.
Ya Tuhan.
[GROANING]
You're cool you're cool.
Aku baik-baik saja.
You're all good, you're all--,You're all good. You know it.
Aku baik, Aku sangat baik-baik saja,aku tau itu.
It's fine.,It's just a bunch of meat.
Tenang, hanyalah seonggok daging.,Ayolah.
Come on. You're good.
[PANTING]
Excuse me.
Permisi.
Excuse me. You. Yes, you.
Permisi. Kau. Ya, kau.,Bisa aku bicara?
May I talk to you?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.,Ini private property.
This is private property.
Just a minute.,I-- I wanna talk to you.
Hey, hey, hey.,Ini private property.,- Sebentar. Aku ingin bicara denganmu.,- Tidak, tak tertarik.
No, no, not interested. Come on.,SKYLER: Hey, don't touch me.
- Sebentar. Aku ingin bicara denganmu.,- Tidak, tak tertarik.,- Ayolah.,- Hey, jangan menyentuhku, jangan.
Do not touch me.
- Ayolah.,- Hey, jangan menyentuhku, jangan.
All right, all right, look not touching, okay?,Not touching here.
- Ayolah.,- Hey, jangan menyentuhku, jangan.,Baiklah. Lihat, tanpa menyentuh.
Look, lady whatever you're selling,,I ain't buying, yo.
Dengar, mbak, apapun yang anda jual aku takkan beli, yo.
Well, my name,is Skyler White, yo.
Well, namaku Skyler White, yo.,Istrinya Walter White, yo.
My husband,is Walter White, yo.
Uh-huh.
He told me everything.
Ia memberitauku segalanya.
Seriously?
Ia memberitauku segalanya.,- Benarkah?,- Ya benar.
That's right.
- Benarkah?,- Ya benar.
And just so you know,
- Benarkah?,- Ya benar.,Dan asal kau tau saudara iparku agen DEA...
my brother-in-law,is a DEA agent
Dan asal kau tau saudara iparku agen DEA...
and I will not hesitate,to call him.
...dan aku takkan ragu,untuk meneleponnya. Paham?
Not if I have to.,Understood?
This is your one,and only warning.
Ini peringatan pertama dan terakhirmu.
Do not sell marijuana,to my husband.
Ini peringatan pertama dan terakhirmu.,Jangan lagi jual ganja ke suamiku.
Okay.,I mean it.
- Okay.,- Aku sungguh-sungguh. Jangan menelepon lagi.
Don't call our house again.
You stay away from him, or,you will be one sorry individual.
Menjauhlah darinya atau kau akan menyesal.
You get me?
- Paham?,- Ya, yeah.
I-- I, uh, think so, yeah.
Um, no more marijuana.,Mm-hm.
- Paham?,- Ya, yeah.,Tak ada ganja lagi. Paham.
I can-- I can dig it.
Tak ada ganja lagi. Paham.
You can dig it. Wonderful.
Tak ada ganja lagi. Paham.,Bagus.
Not that it's any,of my business,
Aku tau ini bukan urusanku tapi mungkin kau harus pertimbangkan...
but you might wanna consider,a different line of work.
Aku tau ini bukan urusanku tapi mungkin kau harus pertimbangkan...,...pekerjaan yang lain.
Okay.
...pekerjaan yang lain.,Okay.
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTING AND PANTING]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.,Mari lakukan dirumahmu, yo.
Let's go to your house you know.
Makes perfect sense.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.,Mari lakukan dirumahmu, yo.,Masuk akal. Mari kita,rusak rumahmu...
Let's, uh...
Masuk akal. Mari kita,rusak rumahmu...
[GASPING]
let's completely screw up,your house
Masuk akal. Mari kita,rusak rumahmu...
so you never wanna spend,another night in it.
...agar kau takkan mau,tinggal lagi. Tentu, mengapa tidak?
Sure. You know, why not?
[GRUNTING]
...agar kau takkan mau,tinggal lagi. Tentu, mengapa tidak?
Yeah, and how's about I send,over my psycho-bitch wife
Yeah, bagaimana bila aku kirim,istri gila ku...
to, uh, you know, break your,balls and threaten you?
Yeah, bagaimana bila aku kirim,istri gila ku...,...untuk, kau tau menakutimu?
God, that would be hilarious you know.
...untuk, kau tau menakutimu?,Tuhan, pasti akan konyol.
And then, you know the killer in the basement,
Tuhan, pasti akan konyol.,Dan kemudian pembunuh di basement...
the one who's completely,my responsibility,
Dan kemudian pembunuh di basement...,...yang harusnya menjadi,tanggung jawabku...
hell, let's just,let him live down there.
...yang harusnya menjadi,tanggung jawabku...,...hell, biarkan saja,dia hidup.
Just, I don't know, make sure,to feed him, like,
Dan jangan lupa memberinya,makan, 3x sehari.
three times a day.
Sure, why not?,It's been really amazing.
Tentu, mengapa tidak? Luar biasa trims untuk kesempatan yang diberikan.
Thank you so much,for the opportunity.
I always dreamt about I don't know, melting bodies.
Tentu, mengapa tidak? Luar biasa trims untuk kesempatan yang diberikan.,Aku selalu bermimpi melelehkan mayat.
[JESSE WHIMPERS,THEN COUGHS]
[GROANING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
You got a brother,in the goddamn DEA?
Kau punya saudara,anggota DEA?
What?
- Apa?,- Kau bilang...
You said you were just doing,some ride-along.
- Apa?,- Kau bilang...,...hanya ikut tur polisi. Kau punya,saudara anggota DEA, ya apa tidak?
Yes or no, do you have a brother,in the DEA?
...hanya ikut tur polisi. Kau punya,saudara anggota DEA, ya apa tidak?
He's a brother-in-law.
- Ia iparku.,- Well, takkan ku khawatirkan.
Oh, well, there's a load,off my mind.
Where did you hear that?
- Ia iparku.,- Well, takkan ku khawatirkan.,Darimana kau tau?
Your freaking wife told me
Darimana kau tau?,Istrimu yang memberitauku,disini ketika aku sibuk.
when she was here,all up in my shit.
Istrimu yang memberitauku,disini ketika aku sibuk.
Yeah, that's right.
Istrimu yang memberitauku,disini ketika aku sibuk.,Yeah, benar.,Ia hampir memergokiku memindahkan Emilio.
She almost caught me,moving Emilio.
Yeah, benar.,Ia hampir memergokiku memindahkan Emilio.
Good job on wearing,the pants in the family.
Yeah, benar.,Ia hampir memergokiku memindahkan Emilio.,Kerja bagus sebagai,kepala rumah tangga.
And why'd you go and tell her,I was selling you weed?
Kerja bagus sebagai,kepala rumah tangga.,Dan mengapa kau bilang,aku jual ganja untukmu?
Because somehow,it seemed preferable
Karena entah mengapa,sepertinya itu lebih baik...
to admitting that I cook,crystal meth and killed a man.
Karena entah mengapa,sepertinya itu lebih baik...,...daripada "aku masak meth,dan membunuh orang".
[SNIFFING]
Is that what I think it is?
Apa itu seperti yang kukira?
Yeah. Yeah, it is.,I smoked a bowl.
Apa itu seperti yang kukira?,Yeah. Yeah, memang. Aku menghisapnya.,Lalu? Rumahku, peraturanku.
So what?,My house, my rules.
Yeah. Yeah, memang. Aku menghisapnya.,Lalu? Rumahku, peraturanku.
Hey, no, no.,Hey, don't give me that, okay?
Yeah. Yeah, memang. Aku menghisapnya.,Lalu? Rumahku, peraturanku.,Hey, tidak, tidak.,Jangan seperti itu, okay?
I held up my end.
Hey, tidak, tidak.,Jangan seperti itu, okay?,Aku sudah lakukan tugasku Emilio. Kau masih bermain-main...
I already took care,of Emilio.
Aku sudah lakukan tugasku Emilio. Kau masih bermain-main...
You're still diddling around,trying to get your nut up.
Aku sudah lakukan tugasku Emilio. Kau masih bermain-main...,...mengumpulkan keberanian.,- Yeah, well, boo-hoo.
Yeah, well, boo-hoo.
...mengumpulkan keberanian.,- Yeah, well, boo-hoo.
I have the truly awful job here.
...mengumpulkan keberanian.,- Yeah, well, boo-hoo.,Tugasku lah yang terberat.
Oh, you wanna-- You wanna talk,awful? You wanna go there?
Tugasku lah yang terberat.,Ingin bicara mengerikan?,Kau tak ingin kesana?
Try dragging 200 pounds of stink,up a flight of stairs.
Ingin bicara mengerikan?,Kau tak ingin kesana?,Cobalah menyeret daging bau 200 pound,naik lewat tangga.
I barely got him in the bathtub.
Cobalah menyeret daging bau 200 pound,naik lewat tangga.,Untung sudah di bathtub.
Bathtub, what...?,What do you mean, bathtub?
Untung sudah di bathtub.,Bathtub, apa?,Apa maksudmu, bathtub?
You know and that's another thing.
Ada lagi. Mengapa kau suruh,aku keliling kota...
Why you got me,running around town
trying to find,some stupid piece of plastic
Ada lagi. Mengapa kau suruh,aku keliling kota...,...mencari plastik tak berguna...
when I have a perfectly good tub,I can use?
...mencari plastik tak berguna...,...ketika ada yang sempurna,yang bisa digunakan?
Oh, God.
Ya Tuhan.
Hey. Hey.
[DRIPPING]
[HISSING]
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry, what were you,asking me? Oh, yes.
Maaf, kau tanya apa?,Oh, ya.
That stupid plastic container,I asked you to buy.
Maaf, kau tanya apa?,Oh, ya.,Plastik tak berguna Yang aku suruh kau membelinya.
You see, hydrofluoric acid,won't eat through plastic.
Kau tau, cairan hydrofluoric,tak bisa menembus plastik.
It will, however, dissolve,metal, rock, glass, ceramic.
Tapi itu bisa, melarutkan logam batu, kaca, keramik.
So there's that.
Jadi begitulah.
[GLEN PHILLIPS' "THE HOLE",PLAYS]
BOY:,Here I go.
Ayo.
DOWNLOADED FROM WWW.AWAFIM.TV
For latest movies and series with subtitles,Visit    WWW.AWAFIM.TV    Today
Ayo.